

### NIRANJAN PATIL

niranjan1911



**Analytics Specialist** 

niranjanpatil391312@gmail.com



Pune, India



#### **SUMMARY**

Senior Analyst with experience in analyzing, evaluating, and improvising business systems for a wide range of organizations. Data Analytics, Ad-Hoc Analysis, Leadership and Project Management, and Business Solution Translation. Innovative specialist with a long history of exceeding client expectations by thoroughly understanding problems and providing creative solutions. keeps well informed of pertinent legislation and regulations.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Pune Institute of Computer Technology(PICT)/Pune

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology 2018 – 2021

# Institute of Civil and Rural Engineering/Kolhapur

Engineering Diploma (Computer Engineering) 2015 – 2018

#### SKILLS

- Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager
- Tealium IQ and EventStream
- Web and App Analytics
- Google Optimize(A/B Testing), Google Firebase(Analytics)
- Data Analytics, Data Visualization
- Web development(HTML, CSS, Javascript), Java, C++, MySQL

### CERTIFICATIONS

- GA4 Certification by Google (2023)
- Tealium (Advanced) (2023)
- Firebase Analytics by google (2023)

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Analytics Implementation Specialist**

DataVinci PVT /(Incubeta SA) | 2022 - Present

- Analytics implementation (GA4) for Web and App, Analysis, and Reporting.
- Responsible for the complete implementation cycle. Proficient in third-party tag implementation.
- Successfully implemented Facebook CAPI, Consent Mode, Google Enhanced conversion, and Server side tracking projects with Google Tag Manager.
- Tealium IQ/Event stream specialist, Implemented GA4 tagging, worked with Tealium to implement Facebook CAPI to achieve Event deduplication and Event matching.
- Perform in-depth analysis of information from multiple data sources (web analytics data as well as external data) and provide significant insights into factors impacting online results.
- Successfully handled and configured an end-to-endOffline to Online conversions for Google Ads using Enhanced Conversions.

#### Application Development Associate Accenture PVT LTD | 2021- 2022

• Worked with the SAP COE team to manage storefront content and communicate closely with the market to solve CDC issues.